== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Amy:)So, have you been having
any morning sickness?
(Howard:)A little.
(Bernadette:)And it doesn't help
(Bernadette:)that I've got this heightened
sense of smell.
(Penny:)Is that a pregnancy thing?
Yeah.
(Bernadette:)The other day I sniffed out
(Bernadette:)where Howie
hid the Girl Scout cookies.
(Bernadette:)No more Tagalongs, my ass.
(Penny:)But now you'll be able to make
(Penny:)your own milk
to eat the cookies with.
(Raj:)Hey, guys. Hey, Penny.
(Raj:)I really appreciate
you helping me with this.
(Raj:)I don't know what to do.
(Penny:)Oh, sure. Let me see it.
See what?
(Raj:)I hadn't spoken to Emily
since I broke up with her,
(Raj:)and she left this
on my doorstep with a note.
“Raj, I got you this before we
split up, but couldn't return it
“and thought
you'd like to have it.
(Penny:)Happy belated
Valentine's Day, Emily.”
(Attorney:)That's nice.
(Penny:)Nice, or is she trying
to manipulate him?
(Raj:)I know. I mean, do I open it?
Do I return it?
(Amy:)Why wouldn't you open it?
(Raj:)Well, she was pretty mad.
(Raj:)For all I know
it's a voodoo doll of me
(Raj:)with a fork stuck in my junk.